Steppenwolf's Arrival
Chapter 2
Wonder Woman Engages
Chapter 3
Cyborg & Flash Coordinate
Chapter 4
Speed Force
Chapter 5
Cyborg's Sonic Blasts
Chapter 6
The Flash Trips and Falls Down the Stairs During the Assault
Chapter 7
Batman Grapples the Parademons
Chapter 8
Aquaman Enters the Fray
Chapter 9
The Lasso of Truth Strike
Chapter 10
Steppenwolf Overpowers Cyborg
Chapter 11
Civilian Truck Escape
Chapter 12
Alfred Monitors from the Batcave
Chapter 13
Barry Runs East to Build Charge
Chapter 14
Superman Returns
Chapter 15
The Kryptonian Dodges the Axe With Utter Ease
Chapter 16
The Justice League Assembles
Chapter 17
Steppenwolf's Final Stand
Chapter 18
Hacking the Motherboxes
Chapter 19
The Unity Synchronization and Impending Destruction of Earth
Chapter 20
Superman and Cyborg Pull the Boxes Apart
Chapter 21
The Explosion and Aftermath
Chapter 22
Truck Breaks Down - Battery Dead
Chapter 23
Justice League Triumphant